{
  "version": 2.0,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Gas used for underwater welding is",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Acetylene",
        "b": "Gasoline",
        "c": "Hydrogen",
        "d": "None"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "Acetylene's chemical formula is",
      "answers": {
        "a": "C<sub>2</sub>H<sub>2</sub>",
        "b": "C<sub>4</sub>H<sub>4</sub>",
        "c": "C<sub>2</sub>H<sub>6</sub>",
        "d": "C<sub>2</sub>H<sub>5</sub>OH"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
{
      "question": "What kind of reaction takes place during oxyacetylene cutting?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Endothermic",
        "b": "Exothermic",
        "c": "None",
        "d": "Both (a) and (b)"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
{
      "question": "Which one of the following gases is complicated to store?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Oxygen",
        "b": "Acetylene",
        "c": "Both (a) and (b)",
        "d": "None"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
{
      "question": "Which part of an oxy-acetylene flame has the highest temperature?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Innermost cone",
        "b": "Outer cone",
        "c": "Intermediate cone",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
{
      "question": "Stream of oxygen jet is required in",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Gas cutting",
        "b": "Gas welding",
        "c": "Brazing",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
{
      "question": "Oxygen-rich flame is used to join",
      "answers":{ 
        "a": "Carbon steels",
        "b": "Copper alloys-brass,bronze",
        "c": "Both (a) and (b)",
        "d": "None of theabove"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
{
      "question": "The ratio of Acetylene to Oxygen, when neutral flame created is",
      "answers":{ 
        "a": "2:1",
        "b": "1:2",
        "c": "1:1",
        "d": "3:1"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
{
      "question": "Central aperture diameter of gas cutting torch varies with",
      "answers":{ 
        "a": "Thickness of material",
        "b": "Type of material",
        "c": "Both (a) & (b)",
        "d": "None"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
{
      "question": "Acetylene gas is stored in the cylinder by mixing with",
      "answers":{ 
        "a": "Alcohol",
        "b": "Acetone",
        "c": "Acetic acid",
        "d": "Folic acid"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    }
]
}





